Yeah, I mean he lost some money, I
guess. Probably not not too much of a of
a loss for him.
Yeah, I mean uh
you know what what this organization
does is treat special teams as an actual
third of the uh of what the game is,
which is what it is. And uh you know
when you have Jay Harvaugh leading us in
what he does um and the guys buy in and
you have guys that take pride in special
teams. Um obviously you know there's
been games all year where we've either
flipped games or you know started the
onslaught um to win games. So uh you
know you can't say enough about you know
the guys that take pride in that and in
the group that we have. Um, you know,
Dicko was pinning guys. I mean, how many
do you have inside the 10? Yeah. I mean,
he's the best in the world at what he
does. Um, and he proved it today. So,
yeah. I mean, just
we [clears throat] take pride in in in
special teams. Um,
and obviously it showed this year that
it can really do wonders for our team.
>> But how does it feel to see others?
>> Yeah, it's amazing. Um,
you know, you you never you always want
to be here, obviously, like you always
dream about playing the Super Bowl. Um,
and you know, some of us it took a
little bit longer to get there and uh
and to win it, but um you know, just
that locker room and what we had all
year was amazing. It was a great
experience, great relationships, and uh
yeah, I mean, it's just there's no words
to express what what that team is in
there.
>> Jason, you set a new record points in a
season. First time anyone's ever done it
in the NFL. What's your reaction to
doing that in a game that you win the
Super Bowl?
>> Yeah. I mean, it doesn't I mean, even
even just winning right now, it doesn't
even feel real, but um you know, you
hear those those numbers being thrown
out there. It's just you know, we've had
amazing defense, obviously, amazing
special teams and offense just moved the
ball so great all year. So, um you know,
as a specialist, you can't really force
force the game, right? Like you get
limited opportunities and uh whenever
your number is called, you just go out
there and do your best.
of the game.
>> No, I mean I I I ride I ride it on my
wrist. I just go one for one. Um
whatever kick that is in front of me, I
just make that my best my best effort
and uh you know, put all my hard work
and you know, all these years and all
the offseason and just, you know, put
that to work and uh yeah, I I just
honestly I I truly go one kick at a
time. So whatever happens,
>> think about the identity of this team
now.
What would you describe as kind of like
who you guys are?
>> I mean, people first. It's this is, you
know, especially, you know, this week
with the media and stuff. Um, you get
asked a lot of questions and, uh,
[snorts]
it it feels weird when you say it so
many times about how close this team is,
like you you you think that people are
think that you're just forcing that and
saying that, but honestly, since April,
this team has been extremely tight. Um,
you know, just every week it's just it's
an amazing experience in that locker
room, the whole organization. Uh, so I
think that really carried us through the
entire year.
>> Uh, I mean, he he gives us opportunities
to build relationships with guys in the
locker room. Um, you know, we do a lot
of off the- field stuff together. Um,
but also like just him and John just
bring in such great guys. Like, you
know, I've been this is my 11th year in
the league and there's there's always
been, you know, a few guys that, you
know, maybe stand out in a team, but
this team there's, you know, from the
older guys to the younger guys that got
drafted. It's there's there's no egos on
this team. Um, it's just everybody
playing for the guy next to them. And,
uh, obviously that showed today.
>> What was that moment like when it seemed
inevitable the last couple of minutes,
but when the clock finally hit zero and
it was clear you were a Super Bowl
champion? Yeah, I mean it still doesn't
feel real. Um I think maybe in a couple
weeks when I go home and see my family
and friends, maybe we'll set in a little
bit more, but right now I'm just enjoy
enjoying the moment with, you know, the
guys that in that locker room, all the
coaches, staff, everybody, players. We
just, you know, we just put so much
work, so much energy into just building
relationships that it's just Yeah, it's
just been amazing.
>> What's it like being go to kicking and
when did you know you were
>> I mean, I was kind of a late bloomer
going to kicking. Uh I played soccer
growing up, but um I remember the first
time I kicked a football uh just fell in
love with it and uh I'm glad I made the
switch from soccer to uh kicking
footballs.
>> Describe the journey of know being
teammates with Williams, you know, other
guys and then being a part of the team
that has
>> Yeah, I mean a lot of questions asked
about Sam obviously this week. Um I
think it's been the same answer for
everybody. Sam's been the same guy um
from 2008 when I played with them with
the Jets to now. Um he's he's he's just
one of the guys, right? Like he's just
uh he's great in the locker room. I knew
he'd fit in right away when we signed
him here. Um and uh when I mean it's
it's just any person, right? Like you
alone if if somebody gives you
confidence, you're you're going to do
better in life, right? So, um, that's
what this organization is all about is
just building up people and just, uh,
building up their confidence and just
letting them know that they're
appreciated. And, uh, obviously he took
us to, uh, the promised land.
>> And Jason, speaking of your journey, how
long have you?
>> Uh, yeah, I texted some people last
night. Um, just told them I appreciate
them. uh that I work with daily or
weekly. Um and you know, honestly, the
road that I've taken personally is is uh
it's it's built me into who I am as a
person and as a as a player in the NFL.
So, um you know, it wasn't always the
easiest, but I'll definitely always
take that for what it is and remember
that for uh building me into the man I
am today.
>> There's a Japanese from watching on
YouTube. So what is the key to handling
the pressure like this very hard
crowding?
>> What's that again?
>> Uh what is the key to handling that
pressure and succeeding in the heavy
crowding?
Yeah, I mean it's you know personally
for me it's just been you know a lot of
years of work and uh you know work on
myself as a person, work on myself as a
as a kicker and just uh
yeah I mean it's just you you just you
just keep working. Um you know I never
thought I'd be in the NFL and to win a
Super Bowl is is an amazing feeling. So,
um,
yeah, I mean, I I wouldn't trade my my
path. And, you know, there's there's so
many different paths in this world to,
uh, to make it as in in into the, you
know, the player that you want to be.
So, um, yeah, I there's just so many
different paths and it doesn't always
have to be perfect. You if you just keep
working, uh, you can you can do what you
want.
>> Jason,
>> one last question.
What was your highlight?
Uh just just seeing my teammates after
the game. Uh yeah, it's just amazing
feeling just, you know, watching the
brothers that you put so much work in
together um succeed and and make it to
this to this spot in life. It's it's
amazing feeling.
>> Yeah. Appreciate it.